<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="sweets_title">Sweets</string>
    <string name="dishes_title">Main Dishes</string>
    <string name="set1_applepie">Preparation time: 60 minutes\n

Cooking time : 45 minutes\n
Ingredients:\n

2.5 cups flour .\n
1 cup unsalted butter , cut into small pieces .\n
1/4 cup water.\n
2 m / k sugar.\n
1/2 m / y salt.\n
Stuffing amounts\n
6 large beads apple cut BBC slices .\n
1/4 cup brown sugar .\n
1/4 cup white sugar .\n
1 m / k cinnamon .\n
1 m / k lemon juice .\n
1.5 m / k cornstarch .\n
How to prepare:\n
\n
Prepared food Mix the flour with the salt and sugar on low speed , then add the butter cubes and iced water and mix on medium speed until Blended all the components .\n
You can add another quarter of a cup of water if the dough is cohesive.\n
The dough is divided into two parts , wrapped with paper and leave in the refrigerator for an hour.\n
In the meantime, cut apples into slices and add a lemon and sugar and leave for 30 minutes and then filtered from the liquid.
On the surface of the table and sprinkled with a little flour devotes the first half of the dough and placed in a glass mold then encases the mold and leave in the refrigerator for 30 minutes.\n
Also singled out the other half and leaves on a tray baking sheet and put in the fridge .\n
Template out of the freezer and add him apples and distributes well and then closed half the other Mufrod .
And close on some good halves .\n
By a sharp knife works 4 slots in the middle of the pastry to allow the steam out during baking .\n
Apple pie left in the fridge for another 30 minutes before baking.\n
In the meantime, heat oven at 170 degrees.\n
Bake in the oven for 45 minutes.\n
Can fat apple pie from abroad Blended egg with ¼ cup cream before putting them in the oven (optional)\n</string>
    <string name="set1_blueberrycheesecake">Preparation time:\n
20 minutes\n
Cooking time :\n
\n
You do not need to cook oven\n
Ingredients:\n
\n
Cranberry tray\n
A quarter cup of water\n
3 tablespoons milk powder\n
150g butter\n
Cream tray\n
3 cans Dream Whip cream\n
8 grains of Philadelphia cheese or Kerry, cheese ( as available )\n
2 baguettes biscuits comminuted\n
Method:\n
\n
- Put the butter in a suitable container on the backburner until completely dissolved .\n
\n
- Put crumbled biscuits , and well Adekém .\n
\n
- Put a layer of the mixture in a buttered biscuits template file your Keck Baltchez , or in separate bowls dedicated to offer .\n
\n
- Mix all remaining ingredients in a blender , a cheese , water , stones , cream , milk powder only without berries .\n
\n
- Now Apply the mixture on the record layer biscuits , and do not forget a good distribution of the mixture by spoon .\n
\n
- Finally Put the cups or template file in the refrigerator for at least 5 hours , and then decorating the surface of cheesecake Cranberry and serve cold \n</string>
    <string name="set1_butteredcookie">Preparation time: 20 minutes\n
Cooking time : 15-20 minutes\n
Ingredients:\n
\n
1/2 cup butter at room temperature .\n
1/4 cup sugar .\n
1 pill eggs .\n
1/2 m / y vanilla .\n
1/2 cup flour .\n
Pinch of salt .\n
1/4 cup almond flour .\n
1 m / p honey dissolved in a tablespoon of water .\n
How to prepare:\n
\n
By electric Tennis fail well the butter with the sugar until the sugar dissolves completely and then add the egg and vanilla bean with continued whipping .\n
Sift the flour with a pinch of salt .\n
Add the almond flour and flour to the butter mixture and mix well , then add the honey mixture with continued whipping .\n
Pour the mixture into your bag with sweets and is in the form of circles on the special paper tray for bread and sliced ??almonds can be added .\n
Bake in a hot oven at 170 degrees for 15 minutes or until golden color .\n
Remove from oven and leave to cool completely and then decorate with chocolate sauce\n</string>
    <string name="set1_cheesecakewithdates">Ingredients:\n
1 cup or 100 g of tea biscuits , crumbled\n
2 tablespoons unsalted butter , melted\n
1 tablespoon honey\n
½ cup or 100 g of sugar\n
½ cup or 125 ml of water\n
1 cup or 200 g of dates , skimmed seeds and chopped\n
1 cup or 250 ml of liquid cream , chilled\n
1 ½ cups or 300 g cream cheese\n
1 packet or 170 g of Nestle cream\n
Teaspoon vanilla extract\n
1 ½ tablespoons of powdered gelatin, dissolved in 4 tablespoons of hot water\n
For packaging Jili dates :\n
1 tablespoon of powdered gelatin\n
1/3 cup or 85 mL of water, boiling\n
¼ cup or 65 ml of the syrup\n
1/3 cup or 85 mL of water, cold\n
How to prepare:\n
Mix biscuit crumbs with butter and honey . Rub ingredients fingers parties . Biscuit mix is poured into a bowl cake mold base moving a diameter of 20 cm .\n
Put the sugar , water and chopped dates in a small saucepan and leave to boil and then simmer for 5 minutes and set aside to cool and become room temperature .\n
Fail fresh liquid cream for 5-6 minutes or until almost become a coherent and then placed in the refrigerator.\n
Fail cream cheese , Nestle, cream , vanilla and Mix dates radiator until consolidating mix well . Add the whipped cream to the cheese mixture and mix well.\n
Pour the dissolved gelatin over the cake mix cheese and stir constantly.\n
Pour cheese mixture evenly in the base of the stomach and put in the fridge for half an hour or until it becomes almost intact .\n
Drain jelly packaging dates and pour over the mix . And the mixture is placed in the refrigerator for at least 3 hours or even hold together and it becomes easy to chipping .\n
To prepare the packaging Jili dates : put gelatin with boiling water in a mixing bowl and stir until jelly melts . Add the date paste and cold water and stir.\n</string>
    <string name="set1_cheesecakemochaflavor">Ingredients:\n
- Cheese Cake tray ready.\n
- Tablespoons sugar.\n
- Dissolved tablespoons butter .\n
- Half a cup of cold milk .\n
- Chuck cappuccino mocha flavor .\n
,, Way | | ~
1 - Mix well the contents of the envelope pancake with sugar and butter in a tray , then the pressure on the parties to mix with your fingers or using a large spoon so Ckla aspects of the pie and the pressure on the rest of the mix so that it becomes equal at the bottom of the Chinese.\n
2 - Beat milk with envelope stuffing pie and cappuccino using electrical tennis on low speed until well mixed , then beat for another three minutes on the average temperature\n
Until the mixture becomes thick . Apply the mixture to the pie smoothly.\n
3 - Put the pie in the fridge for at least an hour until ready to serve . The remainder can be stored in the fridge\n</string>
    <string name="set1_cheesecakesnickers">Ingredients:\n

The first layer:\n
2 biscuits Degistv (100 g)\n
1 template butter (113 g) tourist\n
Second layer:\n
Cream (Qamr 170 gm)\n
2 Karima bag powder\n
1/2 cup cold milk\n
\n
The third layer:\n
6 Chocolate Snickers\n
1/3 template butter (113 g 9)\n
1 / cup liquid milk\n
Method:\n
\n
* Milled biscuits then mixed with butter and then singled in the cake.\n
* Confuse the amounts of the second layer in a blender and then pour on the biscuit layer and put in the freezer until completely frozen.\n
* Dissolved Confect Alsnikrz of in a water bath with butter and milk and mix well then leave</string>
    <string name="set1_nutella">Preparation time: 30 minutes\n
Cooking time : minutes\n
Ingredients:\n
\n
A simple and easy way to prepare a favorite fat chocolate for the children. Aeidiha for your children at home with fresh and healthy ingredients .\n
2 cups Hazel\n
Cup powdered sugar\n
1/3 cup unsweetened cocoa powder\n
2 tbsp oil Hazel\n
Vanilla\n
A little salt\n
How to prepare:\n
\n
Keep hazelnuts on a baking tray and wide and introduce a hot oven over medium heat for 12 to 15 minutes , mixing every two minutes so as not to burn.\n
When we observe cracking Foreign hazelnut crust thin and note conversion to golden in color and comes out of the oven and place on a tray and leave until completely cooled .\n
Keep nuts in a bag Hand mix the products even peels off completely and then put it in the prepared food and begin to run until the note turned into a fine paste, hazelnut and shiny , add the remaining ingredients with the continued operation of prepared food until we get a homogeneous mixture .\n
Scrape aspects should be considered during the preparation of the mixture until we do not find in chocolate conglomerates .\n
Hazelnut oil can be replaced with corn oil in case of unavailability of hazelnut oil .\n
Must mobilize chocolate in a sterile glass jars and sealed</string>
    <string name="set1_oreo">Ingredients:\n
30 love Oreo cookies\n
cup butter, melted 1/4\n
Four cans Philadelphia cheese\n
Cup sugar\n
Sprayed Vanlia the\n
4 eggs\n
Cup liquid cream\n
Oreo to beautify the final layer\n
Directions:\n
Cover pot, which will put the ornaments with tin foil\n
Break Oreo in his mill and then add butter and fail well and then put them in the pot and fail cheese in a blender with sugar and then add precious liquid, Alvanlia and mix well
Add the egg and fail every time and then installed in the container and published on the pieces of Oreo  for last layer crushed approximately 10 beads
Put it in the oven text of the hour, in the center of the oven and leave to cool and well-being</string>
    <string name="set1_chocolateswissroll">Preparation time: 20 minutes\n
Cooking time : 20 minutes\n
Ingredients:\n
\n
6 large eggs beads .\n
1/2 cup flour .\n
1/4 cup cocoa.\n
1/4 m / y lemon zest .\n
1/2 m / y vanilla .\n
7 m / k sugar.\n
1 cup whipping cream cold.\n
1/2 cup strawberry pieces .\n
Chocolate sauce for garnish\n
How to prepare:\n
\n
Grease a rectangular tray and then placed buttered baking paper .\n
Heated oven at 170 degrees.\n
Separating the egg yolks from the Albeadz\n
First beat the egg whites with 3 tablespoons sugar until hurt snowy white foam .\n
Beat egg yolks, then with the rest of the amount of sugar , lemon zest and vanilla until were white in color.\n
Sift the flour with cocoa and a pinch of salt .\n
Add the flour mixture to the egg yolk and mix by simple sweets quietly .\n
Add the egg whites gradually in batches and stir from the bottom to the top so quietly until it is to maintain the amount of air in whipping a result .\n
Pour the mixture into Chinese and then reduce the oven temperature to 160 degrees and then for 20 minutes.\n
In the meantime, precious fail with two tablespoons of sugar and a little Alvanay and leave in the refrigerator .\n
Remove from oven and cover clean towel until completely cooled .\n
He graduated from the Chinese and still quietly baking paper .\n
Placed on a baking sheet clean Other\n
Stones added to the cake and then add pieces small then quietly damage using paper and then conclude well and leave inside the baking paper and leave in the refrigerator for two hours.\n
Decorate with chocolate and strawberry sauce before serving</string>
    <string name="set1_chocolate">Preparation time: 20 minutes\n
Cooking time : 35 minutes\n
Ingredients:\n
\n
200 grams dark chocolate .\n
4 m / k espresso coffee .\n
1 m / k honey.\n
100 grams butter .\n
1 cup castor sugar granules.\n
1/4 cup cream .\n
1 1/2 cups flour .\n
2 large eggs pill .\n
11/2 m / y Peking Boders\n
Pinch of salt .\n
Cocoa for garnish\n
How to prepare:\n
\n
 Heat oven to 170 degrees and heat set web shelf at the top .\n
Painted template average Balzbh of the sprinkle a little flour of choclate.\n
In a glass bowl over as much as boiling water put pieces Alhucklana with butter until pieces chocolate melts completely.\n
Add the coffee , honey and raises the combination of the fire.\n
Sift the flour with the baking powder and salt .\n
Add the eggs to the chocolate mixture and beat well by tennis Alkahra?a .\n
Add the sugar and cream and mix well fail .\n
Pour the mixture into a mold and then bake in the oven for 30-35 minutes .\n
Leave to cool and decorate with chocolate and coffee sauce</string>
    <string name="set2_potatostuffedwithtomatosauce">\n
8 	Medium	Potato\n
2 	Tablespoon	Oil\n
500 	G	Minced meat\n
1 	Large onion	Minced onion\n
4 	Clove	Garlic, crushed\n
1 	Teaspoon	Mixed spices\n
1 	Teaspoon	Salt\n
4/1	Teaspoon	Black pepper\n
4/1	Teaspoon	Turmeric\n
4/1	Cup	Minced parsley\n
4/1	Cup	Pine nuts fried\n
4 	Large onion	Tomato quarters\n
2 	Cup	Broth or water\n
1	Teaspoon	Dried mint\n
\n		
1. in a bowl put in plenty of water. Add the tablespoon of salt. \n
________________________________________\n
2. using a vegetable peeler, peel potatoes. \n
________________________________________\n
3. use vegetable potato ravioli gouged. Put the potatoes in salted water cycle. Refrigerate while preparing the meat.\n
________________________________________\n
4. in a medium saucepan put the oil. Place the pot over medium heat to heat the oil.\n
________________________________________\n
5. Add the oil and cook the meat until brown and dry completely.\n
________________________________________\n
6. Add the onion, garlic, pepper, salt, pepper and turmeric. Cook meat with onion until the onion softens.\n
________________________________________\n
7. pour the meat mixture in dish. Add the parsley and pine nuts Move material to mix.\n
________________________________________\n
8. arrange meat in potato beads for you fill up her well.\n
________________________________________\n
9. bring some short edge size range. Place stuffed potatoes in the pot.\n
________________________________________\n
10. in a jug Blender place the tomatoes, broth and Mint. My obsession on medium speed until a smooth sauce. Spread the sauce on the tomato.\n
________________________________________\n
11. Place the pot on the medium heat to boil the sauce. Cover the pot and the blazing fire. Let the potatoes Cook for about half an hour or until completely cooked.\n
________________________________________\n
12. my potatoes stuffed with white rice.\n</string>

 <string name="set2_kapsa">
Ingredients:\n
\n
1 medium onion, diced to small cubes\n
2 tablespoons olive oil\n
2 medium Tomatoes, peeled and diced to small cubes\n
1 garlic clove, crushed\n
2 tablespoons tomato paste\n
1 whole chicken, cut in half\n
1 teaspoon ground cinnamon\n
1 teaspoon ground cardamom\n
1 teaspoon ground ginger\n
1 teaspoon ground coriander\n
1 tablespoon cumin\n
salt\n
pepper\n
basmati rice\n
\n
Directions:\n
\n
1-Put the onions in a medium size pot, drizzle on the olive oil and cook at medium high heat until the onions are yellowish and starting to brown. Then put the garlic, cook for a few seconds then put in the tomatoes, tomato paste, salt, pepper and the spice mix; cook it until it becomes a thick red sauce and the tomatoes are almost melted.\n
2-Put in the chicken halves. Sauté it with the sauce for a few minutes, then poor in some hot water just a little bit over the chicken and bring it to a boil. Then lower the heat to medium low and let it cook for 40-50 minutes or until the chicken is cooked.\n
3-While the chicken is cooking, wash the rice and soak it in cold water for 30 minutes.\n
4-Take the chicken out and put it in a roasting pan. Put in the oven and broil it until it’s golden.\n
5-Drain the rice from water and put it into the chicken broth. Make sure there isn’t a lot of water in the pot.\n
6-Cook it on medium high heat. Let it boil until it is almost dry, but not too dry. Make sure there is a little bit of broth left in the bottom of the pot.\n
7-Lower the heat to very low, cover well and cook for 10 minutes.\n
8-Now all you have to do is uncover, put the rice in a big serving plate, top with the chicken and serve with a yogurt salad or a green salad--enjoy a great Saudi meal.\n
     
 </string>
    <string name="set2_jerich">Ingredients:\n
\n
3 cups of Jericho \n
3\4 cup of Egyptian rice\n 
3 cup of water\n
little cumin\n
Onion \n
lemon salt\n 
2 cup milk \n
\n
ingredients of koshnh ;\n
a very small section of onion\n
condiment \n
margarine\n
little of oil\n
\n
Directions of koshnh :\n

1-stir onions at small high heat until the onions are yellowish and starting to brown then clos the fire and add margarine.\n
\n
Direction :\n
\n
1- cut onions\n
2-placed upon the cereal mixture with rice and pinch cumin and salt and add the boiling water, stir and then placed on the backburner in the oven for two hours\n
3- stir from time to time ,after cereal become a mellowness and ending has water then add the milk, stir and simmer until the harmony and dissolves cereal.\n
4-get cereal out of the oven and koshnh on it.</string>
    <string name="set2_aareekah">Ingredients:\n
\n
2 Cup of flour\n
Salt\n
1 1\2 cup of water\n
\n
Direction:\n
\n
1-mix the flour with water and stir it again and again .\n
2- then put it in plate then in oven until it become ready .\n
3- get it out of the even and mix it again.\n
4- now we try to make it look like plate like in the picture\n
5- put the honey in the middle \n
6- finally if you want you can add tamer.</string>
    <string name="set2_aseedah">Ingredients:\n
\n
2 cup of flour\n
Salt\n
Water\n
\n
  Direction:\n
1-at medium high heat put the pot that contains the flour and salt.\n
2-slowly add the water while we mix the dough.\n
3-When it become brown turn off the heat .\n
4-But it in plate \n
5-Now it is ready to eat and we can add some milk and broth.</string>
    <string name="set2_spaghetti">Ingredients:\n
1 box macaroni.\n
3 tomatoes\n
salt\n
1 minced meat.\n

Directions\n
1- Boil water for macaroni.\n
2- add salt if you want.\n
3- in other pot we put the minced meet with the chopped tomatoes and salt ,leave it till it done.\n
4-when macaroni is ready we put it in plate and add the meet on it.</string>
    <string name="set2_pizza">Ingredients:\n
\n
180 g plain white flour\n
1 tsp salt\n
1 tsp dried yeast\n
1/2 tsp caster sugar\n
1 tbsp olive oil\n
120 ml warm water\n
2 bowls\n
1 spoon\n
1 rolling pin\n
1 measuring jug\n
1 sieve\n
1 circular baking tray\n
\n
Directions\n
\n
1-Place the saucepan on a medium heat, add the olive oil and butter and allow it to melt. Now add the chopped onions and garlic and stir. Let it cook down for 3-4 minutes until the onions are soft and transparent.\n
2-To the saucepan, add the tomatoes, oregano, basil and tomato puree. Season with a little salt and pepper and stir well. Bring the sauce to a boil and turn the heat down to a simmer. Allow it to cook for 20 minutes.\n
3-For pizzas, allow the sauce to cool before using. This sauce can be stored in a container for a week in the fridge.</string>
    <string name="set2_creamofchickensoup">Ingredients:\n
\n
65 g butter\n
1 medium onion, chopped\n
3 celery sticks, chopped\n
3 medium carrots, chopped\n
3 tbsp flour\n
1 1/2 ltr chicken stock\n
3 sprigs of parsley\n
3 sprigs of fresh thyme\n
1 bay leaf\n
480 g chicken, cooked and diced\n
2 tbsp thick cream\n
2 1/2 tsp dry sherry\n
1 tbsp salt\n
black pepper, to taste\n
\n
Directions\n
1-To begin, put the butter into the saucepan, place it over a moderate heat and allow the butter to melt.\n
2-Next add the carrots, onions, and celery. Gently fry them for ten minutes.\n
3-When the vegetables are soft, add the flour and continue cooking for another couple of minutes, stirring constantly.\n
4-Next, pour in the chicken stock and continue to stir the ingredients as it comes to a boil. Skim the surface occasionally.\n
5-Now, add the parsley, thyme, and the bay leaf to the soup.\n
\n
6-Lower the heat and leave the soup to simmer for fifteen minutes.\n
7-After fifteen minutes, stir in the chunks of chicken and bring back to the boil for a few minutes. Remove the pan from the heat.\n
8-Now add the thick cream, the sherry, the salt, and season to taste with black pepper. Whisk all of these ingredients in well.\n
9-Finally, remove the herbs and for a finishing touch, sprinkle some fresh parsley on top. Serve the soup into bowls.</string>
    <string name="set2_tomatosoup">•	1/3 kg tomatoes, chopped\n
•	2 onions, chopped\n
•	3 garlic cloves, peeled\n
•	2 tbsp tomato puree\n
•	1 ltr chicken or vegetable stock\n
•	10 g butter\n
•	3 tbsp olive oil\n
•	salt and pepper\n
•	1 wooden spoon\n
•	1 sieve\n
•	1 ladle\n
•	1 stick blender\n
1 large bowl\n
\n
1- Place a pan on a medium heat, add the oil and butter, stir well and allow to melt.\n
2- Once melted add the onions and chopped garlic and stir. Sweat the onions until they have a little colour, stirring occasionally to prevent them from burning.\n
3- Add the tomato puree, chopped tomatoes, stock, stir again and bring it to the boil. Once boiling, cover and turn the heat down to a simmer. Leave to cook for 30 minutes. Once cooked, remove from the heat.\n
4- Remove the lid and with your hand blender, pulse to blend the soup into a rough puree, taking care not to raise the stick blender out of the soup! Finally season with salt and pepper.\n
5- Place the sieve over a large bowl and ladle the soup into the sieve. Using the back of the ladle, push the pulp down into the bowl below. Continue until all the soup has been sieved and transfer it back into the pan. Reheat if necessary.\n
6-Pour into soup bowls and add a dash of cream just before serving! Serve with some fresh crusty bread and enjoy!</string>
    <string name="set2_beeftagin">1 	Km	Meat with bone\n
1/2	Teaspoon	Turmeric\n
1/2	Teaspoon	Paprika\n
1/2	Teaspoon	Coriander\n
1/2	Teaspoon	Cinnamon\n
1/2	Teaspoon	LEA\n
1/2	Teaspoon	Garlic powder\n
1/2	Teaspoon	Onion powder\n
1/2	Teaspoon	Ginger\n
1/2	Teaspoon	Black pepper\n
2 	Teaspoon	Salt\n
3 	Tablespoon	Olive oil\n
20 	Bead	Small onions\n
20 	Clove	Garlic correctly\n
3 	Large onion	Tomatoes, peeled, chopped\n
2 	Tablespoon	Vinegar\n
2	Tablespoon	Pomegranate molasses\n
To apply:	Minced parsley. Rice noodle\n
		
1. in a large bowl place the meat pieces.\n
________________________________________\n
2. in a small bowl place the cumin, turmeric, paprika, Pepper, coriander, cinnamon, cardamom, garlic, onion, ginger, pepper and salt. Stir spices to mix. \n
________________________________________\n
3. spread one-third of the amount of the spices on the meat and scrape off.\n
________________________________________\n
4. in a saucepan deep thick base put the oil. Place the pot over medium heat. Put a few pieces of meat in the pot. Cook meat to dark brown in color. Transfer the meat to a side dish. Add the rest of the meat and cook until golden. Transfer to a dish.\n
________________________________________\n
5. in the same pan, add the onion and garlic. Cook onion and garlic for a few minutes, then add the tomatoes and cook over high heat. Return the meat to the pot. Arrange the rest of the mixture of spices. Dot with vinegar and pomegranate molasses. Cover the pot and let the meat over medium heat for 10 minutes, then add the amount of 2/1 cup of water. Cover the pot and the blazing fire. Let the meat simmer for 90 minutes with the addition of a little water every 20 minutes if the decreased amount of water.\n
________________________________________\n
6. in a deep serving dish pour beef Tagine with onions and garlic, then garnish with parsley. Serve immediately with rice noodle casserole</string>

</resources>